https://www.his.se/dataprivacy/

Search results
Show all results for ""
Can not find any results or suggestions for "."
Job Opportunities
How can we help?
Contact Us
Find Employees
Close
EducationQ&A for students in regard to Covid-19AdmissionHow to ApplyPrerequisitesPrior Learning and ExemptionsAcademic YearDegree Seeking StudentTuition Fees and PaymentGuidelines regarding tuition feesScholarships, grants and loansUniversity of Skövde Master's ScholarshipsApplication for Master's ScholarshipsScholarship ResultsScheduleWebinarStudent SupportStudy and career counsellingStudying at university for those with disabilitiesNewly AdmittedChecklist: admitted through universityadmissions.seChecklist: admitted through antagning.seResidence permit for studiesHealth InsuranceAccommodationConfirmation of stayConditions for accommodationRegistrationInternational introductionCovid-19: Precautions taken to keep campus as safe as possibleExchange Student at the UniversityHow to Apply for Exchange StudiesCourses for Exchange StudentsAccommodation For Exchange Students Study ProgrammesBehavioural sciencesCognitive Neuroscience: Mind and Brain - Master's ProgrammeBioscienceBiomedicine - Study ProgrammeBioscience - Molecular BiodesignMolecular Bioinformatics One-year Master'sBioinformatics - Master's ProgrammeCognitive Neuroscience: Mind and Brain - Master's ProgrammeInfection Biology - Master's ProgrammeMolecular Biotechnology - Master's ProgrammeSustainable Management of Biological Resources - Master's Programme Two-year Master'sBiomarkers in Molecular Medicine - Master's ProgrammeInfection Biology - Master's ProgrammeMolecular Biotechnology - Master's ProgrammeSystems Biology with specialization in Bioinformatics - Master's ProgrammeEngineering and Technology One-year Master'sIntelligent Automation - Master's ProgrammeVirtual Ergonomics and Design - Master's Programme Two-year Master'sIntelligent Automation - Master's ProgrammeVirtual Ergonomics and Design - Master's Programme Related programmeHuman-Robot Interaction - Master's Programme Courses for professionalsThe Virtual FactoryHuman-Robot Collaboration through Integrated Virtual ToolsOptimization methods for industryPossibilities and Benefits of Simulation for Decision SupportTechnical Leadership for Future Industry ProcessesBusiness Intelligence data-driven organizationsIntegrated Virtual CommissioningEngineering Course CombinationsGame DevelopmentExchange Students in Game Development One-year Master'sDigital Narration: Game and Cultural Heritage - Master's ProgrammeGames User Experience - Master's programmeSerious Games - Master's Programme Two-year Master'sGame Development - Master's programmeHealth sciencesBiomedicine - Study ProgrammeCognitive Neuroscience: Mind and Brain - Master's ProgrammeInformatics One-year Master'sData Science - Master's ProgrammePrivacy, Information and Cyber Security - Master's Programme Two-year Master'sData Science - Master's ProgrammePrivacy, Information and Cyber Security - Master's ProgrammeHuman-Robot Interaction - Master's Programme Related programmesBioinformatics - Master's ProgrammeMolecular BioinformaticsSkills developmentCourses for employees working in industryCivilingenjör 4.0Let’s build smart factories togetherPossibilities and benefits of simulation for decision supportOptimization methods for industryHuman-Robot CollaborationIntegrated Virtual CommissioningBusiness Intelligence, data-driven organizationsTechnical Leadership for Future Industry ProcessesContract educationPhD programmesResearchDigital Health Research (DHEAR)Woman, Child, Youth and FamilyA salutogenic perspective on sustainable health in women-dominated workThe Study of Parental SupportDigital Parental SupportSustainable care –with existential health during transition to parenthoodSterile water as pain relief during birthPredictors of mental health in adolescencePublications Woman, Child, Youth and FamilyWellbeing in Long-term Health ProblemsThe 1177 Vårdguiden (VPT) – Care Guide telephone services - and attendance at children’s emergency roomsTo take charge of one's life - group-based education for patients with diabetes type 2 in primary careParoxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)Can digital support be beneficial for elderly people’s oral health?KOLinfo – self-care education using a digital aid for patients suffering from chronic obstructive pulmonary diseaseStudy (of) wellbeing in patients receiving mobile integrated careReflective STRENGTHPublications in Wellbeing in Long-term Health ProblemsTranslational Medicine TRIMEvaluation of new pharmaceutical compounds and their effects in the area of cancer and also in strokeNOX, ROS and metabolism in Pancreatic Ductal AdenocarcinomaFood – Gut – Brain – Mind – HealthGenes as targets for cancer treatmentAffective touch and its effects on the oxytocin systemObesity and androgen excess in women – adiponectin as a new treatment optionNeurogenic disordersPublications Translational Medicine TRIMEnterprises for the FutureProfessional Accounting Practices and SustainabilityKnowledge, Innovation and MarketingInbets BSRFollowership and Organizational ResilienceStrategic EntrepreneurshipInformaticsSoftware Systems Research GroupFOSS4SMEsCISOSSPREFORMAPREFORMA unresolved issuesPREFORMA statementORIOSOpen WatersLIM-ITEventsSUDOSkövde Artificial Intelligence LabBISON: Better decisions through Big DataA smarter society through Big Data analyticsTeamwork through Interaction with Air SystemsData privacy for big dataUnderstanding Human MigrationSwedish MetalPACAInfofusion FusariumIRRAPast projectsFormer membersPublications Skövde Artificial Intelligence LabMedia, Technology and CultureLevel upKastisKIDCOGInclusive game designFrequency MissingHow to make e-sports more spectator-friendlyPublications Media, Technology and CultureInteraction LabDREAMAIRInGaMe LabGame Hub ScandinaviaSweden Game ArenaDescription of Action LibraryPublications Interaction LabInformation SystemsELISAEnterprise modelingDOMECCRAAAFFFTINGPublications Information SystemsDistributed Real-Time SystemsSmartParkELVIRAPast projectsPublications Distributed Real-Time SystemsPrevious group members and studentsSystems biologyCognitive Neuroscience and PhilosophyPublications Cognitive Neuroscience and PhilosophyBiotechnologyArsenic contamination of foodsBioremediation of heavy metalsMolecular methods for species determination of mussels and their larvaeEcological ModelingStudying Nordic brown beesEnd biodiversity loss through improved tracking of threatened invertebratesLandscape biodiversity capacity: a tool for measuring, monitoring and managingWaterAssess: Multi-biomarker panel for environmental impact assessment of wastewater effluentsAdvancing the Metabolic theory of EcologyPast ProjectsPublications Ecological ModelingTranslational BioinformaticsTransplant Tissue EngineeringAlgorOmicsBioMineBiomarkers for disease modellingBiomarkers for toxicity testingstem cell based in vitro modelPast projectsPublications Translational BioinformaticsInfection BiologyFuture diagnostics of sepsisSepsIT® – the development of diagnostic systems for sepsisDetection of plant pathogensEarly diagnosis of sepsismiRSeps - future diagnostics of sepsisProtein interactions in inflammatory diseasesSMARTDIAGNOSBiomarkers in clinical diagnosisVirtual EngineeringVirtual factoriesVirtual Manufacturing ProcessesCoSimPublications Virtual Manufacturing ProcessUser Centred Product DesignSUMMITVIVATACOSynergy Virtual ErgonomicsVirtual DriverVirtual Driver ErgonomicsMOSIMPublications User Centred Product DesignPast research projectsProduction and Automation EngineeringTOPAZMOSIMVISIONREWINDAutoinspectOPTIONTWINMANUWORKProduction of the next generation powertrainsPast ProjectsPublications PATRelated researchPhysics and MathematicsPublications Physics and MathematicsHR Strategy for ResearchersOngoing work with the European Human Resources Strategy for Researchers (HRS4R)Documents and decisions on HRS4R PhDPhD programmesInterested in becoming a PhD student?Enrolled at other universitiesCourses on PhD levelApply for courses on PhD levelReporting of course credits, individual commitments and credit transfersRegulations, forms and templatesContact and supportThe PhD student councilA.I. in research - Panel DiscussionIPSIAugmented Reality Smart Glasses as operator support in assembly: enabling industrial integrationFacility Layout Design with Simulation-based Optimization:
a Framework for Process, Flow, and Layout OptimizationIPSI Digest NewsletterIPSI activitiesAbout usFacts and figuresOrganisationVice-Chancellor, Pro Vice-Chancellor, Deputy Vice-Chancellor and University DirectorThe faculty boardCurriculum CommitteesCurriculum Committee for BioscienceCurriculum Committee for BusinessCurriculum Committee for Health SciencesCurriculum Committee for InformaticsCurriculum Committee for Engineering SciencesSchools at the UniversityThe School of BioscienceThe School of BusinessThe School of Health SciencesThe School of InformaticsThe School of Engineering ScienceInformation regarding covid-19Digitalisation for sustainable developmentQuality managementGoverning documentsData Protection (GDPR)Job opportunitiesAvailable positionsEventsCalendarAcademic CeremonyInternationalisationEducation agentsUse of education agenciesPartner UniversitiesInternational OfficeLibrarySearch and evaluateDatabasesJournalsTips and strategies for searchingEvaluating sourcesBook a librarianAccessing library resourcesLinks to e-resourcesGoogle Scholar and full textBorrow and requestCourse literatureView and renew your loansRequesting articles and booksArticle requestRequest books and suggest acquisitionsLibrary card and lending rulesApply for a library cardTalking books, recorded literatureThe library for distance studentsWrite and citeReferencingEndNoteCopyrightPublishing degree projects in DiVAStudy Support CentreBook a group study roomAbout the libraryThe study environment, facilities and comfortContact and staffLibrary opening hoursContactReceptionFind your way on campusFind employees
Start
About us
Facts and figures
Data Protection (GDPR)
We use cookies on his.se. By continuing to browse you accept the use of cookies.
Ok, I understand
Read more about cookies
Data Protection (GDPR)
The University of Skövde (org.no: 202100-3146) is committed to protecting your privacy, and we process your personal data in accordance with the Swedish Data Protection Act. The University is the Controller for all processing of personal data within the University.
How does the University use the information?
The University processes personal information to fulfil its obligations as a government agency and university, which is to conduct research, provide education and operations in collaboration with the community. We also process personal information to be able to review and develop our operations, and to comply with applicable Swedish laws.
The processing of personal information within the University is connected to these purposes. Only necessary personal information must be processed.
More details on how your specific information is processed is available to you as an employee, student or external party in respective specific descriptions.
What personal information is processed?
There are various reasons for the processing of personal information by the University. The most common reasons are that you are a student, researcher, participant in a study, employee, participant in a conference or other event, applicant for a position of for some other reason have interactions or collaboration with the University.
The type of personal information we process depends on the purpose, and includes but is not limited to the following:
Contact information such as name, address, telephone number and e-mail. The personal identification number is needed to confirm your identity or for coordinating your information between systems to ensure that your information is consistent.
Bank information and other financial information is needed for payment of salary and other reimbursement, or for invoicing purposes.
Personal information collected in the scope of research studies.
Information on study results and other information about your studies at the University or other educational institution.
Information in regards to participation in conferences or courses.
Personal information that is required when you apply for a position at the University, and for processing of employment matters.
Legal basis for the processing
As a government agency and educational institution, and depending on the purpose of the processing, we may use the following legal grounds for processing of personal information:
Information of public interest
Means:Directives from the parliament and the governmentExamples from our operations:EducationResearchCollaborationStudent projects
Performing government duties
Means:Necessary for performing government dutiesExamples from our operations:ExamsDisciplinary matters
Contracts
Means:To fulfil contracts with the data subjectExamples from our operations:Employment contractsCollaboration contractsPurchase contracts
Legal obligations
Means:Complying with laws and regulationsExamples from our operations:Act of public records and archivesWorking Environment ActLaw on annual leave
Consent
Means:Must be voluntary, informed and documented.Examples from our operations:Student projects (if sensitive personal information)Marketing
How we collect your personal data?
We collect most of the information from you directly. In certain cases, we collect information from other sources, such as the Tax Agency, the Swedish Board of Student Finance, Ladok or universityadmissions.se.
Who has access to the personal data?
Much of the information at the University is considered public records. If your personal information is present in a public document, anyone who requests the document will be able to access your personal information, unless the privacy in the Law on Official Secrets and Public Records (2009:400) prevents access.
In addition to relevant members of the staff at the University of Skövde, the information may also be accessed by other government agencies in certain cases. External suppliers of IT-systems may sometimes have access to your personal information. In those cases, contracts are in place to ensure correct and legal processing. In the case of transfer outside the EU/EEC, adequate protection levels must be ensured.
For how long do we retain your personal data?
We retain your personal information for as long as they are needed for the purpose for which they were collected and for as long as is required by law and other regulations. For more information, we refer to the specific descriptions for the respective registration categories.
If you are employed, we process your personal information for as long as it is needed to manage the employment, and after that, for as long as is required by law and other regulations.
If you are a student, we process your personal information for as long as you are a student at the University, and after that, for as long as is required by law and other regulations.
If you are a participant in a study, we process your personal information for as long as it is needed to ensure quality of the research.
The same rules apply for all processing of personal information, regardless of its origin. Personal information in documents is retained in accordance with the Swedish Act of public records and archives (1990:782) and the Public Records Office regulations. In many cases, this means that your personal information will be retained between a number of years and for all future in the University records. In regards to personal information in public records, it may be shared in accordance with the Act on access to public information.
What are your rights?
You have the right to information on how we process your personal information and to have access to the information.
You have the right to correct erroneous information.
In certain cases, you may request to delete the information, that the processing be limited or that the personal information be moved (data portablility).
You have the right to object to the use of your personal information for marketing purposes. In certain cases, you may object to other processing of your personal information.
You have the right to object to automated decision-making and profiling, if applicable.
You have the right to withdraw any consent.
If you believe that we are in violation of the rules for processing of personal information, you may file a complaint with the Data Protection Agency.
Contact us
Requests for extracts from the records, requests for corrections or requests regarding any other rights must be made in writing and be signed by you. Send your request to the Controller.
Controller
Högskolan i SkövdeAddress: Box 408, 541 28 Skövde, SWEDENE-mail: registrator@his.seTelephone: +46 500-44 80 00Organisation number: 202100-3146
If you have any questions about how the University processes your personal information, you may contact the University's data protection officer.
Data protection officer
E-mail: dataskyddsombud@his.se
About usFacts and figuresOrganisationVice-Chancellor, Pro Vice-Chancellor, Deputy Vice-Chancellor and University DirectorThe faculty boardCurriculum CommitteesCurriculum Committee for BioscienceCurriculum Committee for BusinessCurriculum Committee for Health SciencesCurriculum Committee for InformaticsCurriculum Committee for Engineering SciencesSchools at the UniversityThe School of BioscienceThe School of BusinessThe School of Health SciencesThe School of InformaticsThe School of Engineering ScienceInformation regarding covid-19Digitalisation for sustainable developmentQuality managementGoverning documentsData Protection (GDPR)Job opportunitiesAvailable positionsEventsCalendarAcademic CeremonyInternationalisationEducation agentsUse of education agenciesPartner UniversitiesInternational Office
Published: 2/11/2020
Edited: 2/11/2020
Responsible:
webmaster@his.se
